[Music]
hello everybody welcome to the
impressive channel and actress by the
name of Amanda sills has been getting a
lot of backlash ever since she revealed
that she got kicked out of an all-black
Emmys party during the Emmys weekend now
if you don't know who Amanda sills is
amanda has different hats in the
industry she used to be a DJ
she's a radio personality she was
temporarily a part of the musical group
floor tree she's also a stand-up
comedian and she has her own podcast
show called small doses but what most
people know her for is her acting she
started off acting at a young age in the
show my brother and me and now she
currently stars on a hit show on HBO
called and secured now about two weeks
ago
Amanda sills did go on social media and
she revealed that she was ex corded out
of a black hollywood Emmys party I got
to the black Hollywood every party last
night with my homeboy Kendrick and my
homegirl keke and we were being escorted
we're being and turned into the party
when the woman at the door a white woman
named Kiara was like stop she can't go
in like there's just no reason for like
me to be standing out here and being
like told like no you can't go in so
then I was like you know what I'm out so
I go to the curb and then another
homeboy of mine is like what what do you
mean they won't let you in he's like
we're gonna fix that so now like 15
minutes later he comes gets me brings me
back and was like she should be able to
go in and this thing white woman Kiara
is like no she cannot go in she cannot
go in and it was in that moment that I
realized like oh this is like about me
then Elisha Kelly comes out Elisha Kelly
is like walk for you out here and I'm
like I think because this woman will not
let me in and he was like what just just
come in just come in so I'm coming in
and she's like no no and he was like
just go she's gone and I just went and I
was like yeah because I don't know why
this woman is so set bent I mean not
entering this party so when Kiki and I
had got in and she I went one way and I
went the other way by the time she came
back to the bar
she thought that just like I was talking
to people in the party no a security
guard was talking to me because the
security guard was dispatched to come
and remove me from the party yes so I'm
sitting there like I'm not leaving this
party until you tell me who is saying
that I need to leave the party he's like
all right I'm gonna find out so he's
looking like talking on his phone and
then he's like Vanessa Vanessa is saying
that you need to leave the party vanessa
of the ANPR group and i'm like really
that doesn't surprise me
i'm like there is a discussion that
needs to be high because there's no
reason why it's like you're not on the
list and you need to leave you're not on
the list and I was like fine Vanessa
fine Vanessa I would like to have a
discussion with Vanessa because I need
to understand what threat I opposed to
this party there are several people who
are in this party that are not on the
list why am I being singled out
no I don't need to discuss that with you
two more security guards come up and our
good friend Kiara who comes up and says
no I'm the one who said she needs to go
Kiara I'm the one who says she needs to
go I'm the one so I just want to
reiterate for you one more time as I was
saying at this point out loud so let me
just get this straight
I am being escorted out of a black
Hollywood party the only one that
happens for the Emmys I am being
escorted out because this white woman
here says that I can't be in here I just
want to get that clear and y'all saw me
say that in real time on my Instagram
and they were like yes you need to go so
now I start walking out and I turn to
the general manager who has been nasty
since he walked up to me and I was like
this is some bullsh
you doing wrong and as I did this hit
Lackey some white some white boy walks
moves in and presses up against me and
pushes me back yeah it was about to be
worldstar night because I
really I'm not here for being touched
especially by men who are trying to
exert authority for no [ __ ] reason
like you know a lot of times people want
to exert authority but they want to do
it at such an extreme level for no
reason I'm not fighting I'm not loud I'm
not belligerent I'm simply saying I
would like an explanation and they're
saying no you don't deserve an
explanation now I've got four security
guards telling me that I need to get off
the premises immediately and thankfully
the first security guard though he's the
one who stopped it from being a
worldstar night because he was like miss
we don't got to do this we don't got to
do this miss so just for the record
Amanda Steel's I'm not speaking in the
third person I was escorted by four
security guards out of the black
Hollywood Emmy party last night
for simply wanting to get into the black
Hollywood Emmy party last night I saw
hella people come to a party last night
that were not on the list
I literally with Kiki was there when
they put the tighter name and put it on
the list but who didn't want to do that
for me
so that was Amanda telling the full
story about how she got kicked out of
this particular Emmys party and she did
later on reveal that the reason why she
got kicked out is because Isa race
publicist is beeping with her and she
did go into detail about this on her
podcast and I thought it was very
interesting to hear that Amanda was at
odds with somebody from ESA's camp
because this kind of makes it seem as if
there's an issue between Issa and Amanda
now I'm not trying to create any drama
that's not there but I do find it
interesting that Issa Ray's publicist
has an issue with Amanda and I'm
wondering how this will eventually
affect Amanda standing on insecure
because insecure is issa show and she
did bring amanda on there and also
amanda and Issa have worked together in
the past issa did have amanda star in
her webisode series get your life so it
seemed as if they were cool but this
whole few that amanda has what isis
publicist might be affecting that
relationship now amanda did go into
detail about that whole Emmys incident
and
time she named quite a few names when
she told the story again on her podcast
show so a year ago Issa Ray's publicist
Vanessa Anderson of a NPR and some other
people they started doing a black Emmy
party so it's basically like to
celebrate like black Hollywood and you
know just give us a space to come and
celebrate after we do the hobnob at like
the HBO party the Comedy Central party
except excitement so when I arrived at
the party last year I came with Jill
Scott and of course I work with Issa so
vanessa is somebody who I am absolutely
like met before like when I had my web
series on ESA's channel on YouTube and I
have interacted with her you know on a
few occasions but she has never been
nice to me ever like she's always had a
certain like curtness and she's always
seemed to be bothered but simply by just
like my demeanor my way of it my way of
communicating with her etc and at a
certain point it just became well then
this is just not somebody I need to
speak to because I don't work for her
and she doesn't work for me and you know
there's no reason for us to even
interact for all intents and purposes so
we don't you know I say hello to her
like if I see here but there's not gonna
be any like back and forth exchange we
are not friends so last year when I got
to the party I showed up with Jill Scott
and when I came with Jill she said oh
like let me have my manager go to the
front you know just to make everything
smoother so her manager went to the
front and Vanessa was at the front and
her manager like pointed back towards us
and when I was there I looked at Vanessa
and just kind of surreptitiously pointed
toward Jill like look who I'm you know
with because there was a bunch of people
outside too and she just exclaimed I
mean nobody has time for this right now
I do not have time for this and it was
like what's happening so everybody
looked around because like I hadn't said
anything so it was very weird like it
was just out the blue that this person
was having such like a visceral reaction
so I just was like
I was going on and so Jill's manager was
like what the hell was that about
he was like come on so he's like went in
the party and that was that and I went
in the party and um you know I told east
I was like hey you know your publicist
like she's just like she's just not
being nice so she's just nasty and I
don't even need her to be kind I don't
your kindness but just have a certain
layer of civility with me you know and
he's was like yeah I mean that's just
between y'all you know cuz it's her
party so it's not really like my
jurisdiction to tell her how to treat
you at her party okay so I left it at
that
this year Jesse Williams had invited me
to the party and anyone who knows me
knows I don't even like none of this
party but I love a celebration of
blackness and so when I was at the HBO
party I was telling everybody about this
party like you know we have somewhere we
can go celebrate after this so I'm like
telling niecy Nash and I'm telling
Sherri Shepherd and you know just like
everybody I'm running into Kendrick
who's also on and secure who else
breach a web Gabrielle Dennis like just
spread the word so me and Kendrick get
to the party alongside my friend Kiki
who is not in the industry when we get
to the party the girl at the door asks
for Kendricks name and he has a plus one
so I'm his plus one that she asked for
Kiki's name and Kiki's like telling her
her name and she just writes in her
phone it's like okay so we're about to
walk in and then a white woman who has a
clipboard who had not been at the rope
but was in the front area
all of a sudden turns around and points
at me and says no she cannot go in she's
not on the list so then it Elisha Kelly
comes out and Elijah Kelly is like yo
why are you out here and I'm like
because they're not letting me in and at
this point I've already Instagram the
fact that like a white woman is at the
door preventing me from getting into the
black Emme party but you know what is
going on and now I'm starting to get
like
irritated by it because I'm like this is
just foolish like I'm clearly being
targeted here and I don't know why so
what ends up happening is Elijah's like
you know what they're gonna kick me
other parties to come on in so he
welcomes me in and as I'm coming in the
white girl is like her name is Kiera
she's like she cannot throw it she
cannot go in and I was like girls stop
and I just wave her off and I kept
walking so I walk in and I go to the bar
Kiki goes to the bathroom but the time
Kiki has come back from the bathroom a
security guard is talking to me and the
security guard says to me hello miss we
have been asked to escort you out I've
been asked to sort you out I'm like well
who's asked you to skort me out and he
said let me find out so he gets on his
phone and he says Vanessa I said well
then you need to find Vanessa because I
need to speak to Vanessa and I need to
find out from Vanessa why I'm being
escorted out apparently no one could
find Vanessa so Elijah comes over and
he's like what's going on I'm like
they're escorting me out so now he's
trying to find Vanessa J August comes
over and it's like what's going on and
said they're escorting me out he's like
let me go find Vanessa because I was
sitting at the insecure table so there's
a table for insecure that apparently
natasha has ADD and Ivonne Azad and
Kendrick is at but I'm not being allowed
into the party because I'm not on the
list so there's a table for the show
that I am an actual series regular and a
star of but I am not allowed into the
party so much so that a security guard
has now been dispatched to risk or me
out of the party and I'm like I'm not
leaving nowhere until y'all tell me why
I'm being escorted out we don't have to
tell you anything
I said Vanessa is apparently the reason
why I'm being asked to leave and I need
to understand why that is no you don't
you need to get out now or I'm calling
the cops so now I have a security guard
another security guard a third security
guard and a black general manager of
Avenue a Club here in Hollywood telling
me that if I don't leave a party for
black Hollywood that I am going to have
the cops called on me and this is all
because of one black woman named Vanessa
Anderson at the ANPR group
whom I have never done anything to so
I'm like you know what I know because
now I'm also seeing people see this
happen
and they're doing nothing it was all
about we need to get Amanda seals out of
here now and this guy this general
manager I pointed at him and I say you
know you're tough for this and when I do
that
he is other security guards this white
guy gets between us and pushes up
against me and it takes everything
litter I'm not even exaggerating it took
every single ounce of my strength to not
retaliate against that and it was the
nice security guard who was literally in
my ear like you don't have to do this we
don't do this tonight if I saw a black
woman calmly sitting at the bar who I
know is a part of the skin environment
being harassed by security guards there
is no way in hell I'm letting that go
down without making a ruckus and for the
record nobody made a ruckus for me
nobody and the amount of ruckus that I
make for everybody was really like a i
opening and very honestly like delayed I
had a very delayed emotional reaction to
the reality of like y'all does not meet
we just not the same we're not the same
and I may be in this Hollywood [ __ ] but
I ain't y'all it was humiliating
it was humiliating and I was then
escorted out and the security guard who
had been kind the whole time he said I'm
sorry for doing that you know but we
have to do our jobs and I said you know
I don't typically do this I don't
typically do this but I want you to
write down my name because when you look
me up you're gonna realize how
ridiculous it was that you were asked to
remove me from this event because
there's no foundation for me to have
been removed especially in this fashion
from this event in the wake of this I
have talked about it on my Instagram and
I've had some people say things to me
like you're just being
childish she didn't want you at the
party so you shouldn't have been at the
party you shouldn't have any you
shouldn't have any problem with her
wanting you not to be at the party like
it's her prerogative and the reason why
I'm telling this story within the
context of side-effects of
professionalism is for a number of
reasons one this party was not at her
house this was a Hollywood party for
black entertainers and contributors to
Hollywood I am a part of that industry
and should be here celebrating with my
community too she's not the only one
putting this party together there are
other people that are involved I stated
many times I've been invited by Jesse
Williams and I was met with dismissals
and disregard it was shocking to me and
was really shocking Amanda I mean yes
and I had to remain professional and
some people would say well if you were
being professional then you wouldn't
even say who she is that son behavior
does not deserve the luxury of anonymity
and this was an instance where no no no
I'm not gonna have this story told by
other people without me telling my story
after Amanda sills released this episode
of her podcast she did get a lot of
backlash on Twitter surprisingly she got
backlash from her own co-star on the
show and secured
sharona's Jackson he responded to madam
new auras article about Amanda and he
said you can't be a disrespectful human
being and expect people to want to hang
out with you it's quite simple
sit it out so when her own cast mate on
the show said this I was like okay I see
what's happening here
Amanda seems to have rubbed some people
the wrong way and I'm not even sure of
her co-stars from insecure are cool with
her like that because they were sitting
in the party while she was being
exported out so that was very telling to
me and sharona's Jackson wasn't the only
one on Twitter who called Amanda sills
out there are more than a few people who
said she was rude and disrespectful in
person so it kind of seems to me that
amanda has a personality that rubs a lot
of people the wrong
way some people really like her and some
people don't like her at all
I think she's a talented and intelligent
person but I don't think she's that
self-aware she's not very cognizant of
how she might come off to other people
and it's clear that she doesn't take
rejection well if somebody doesn't like
you make a mental note of that and go
you don't have to return that energy but
just go on about your life I think the
fact that she tried to force herself
into a party especially a party that's
being hosted by somebody who does not
care for her it's pointless
she talked about the experience she had
last year where she showed up at this
very same party and the publicist
Vanessa was annoyed with her presence
and she tried to show up again and got
rejected again and I'm just thinking she
should have took the hit the first time
but it is what it is there are some
people who don't like Amanda but there
are a lot of people who do so this is
not a video to make Amanda seem like
she's such a bad person I personally
don't think she's a bad person but I
understand that she's not everybody's
cup of tea anyway tell me what you all
think about this video down below please
like comment and subscribe and share
this video if you care thank you so much
for watching and I'll see you next time
bye
[Music]